duda.co 2017-10-03

# Privacy Policies

#### 1\. General

We at Duda, Inc. (“ **Duda** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **our** ”, or “ **us** ”) very much respect your privacy, are committed to protecting it and want you to be informed about the ways we protect, use and share the information that we collect.

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) serves to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of the information we receive when you visit [www.duda.co](http://www.duda.co/) (together, our “Site”) and when you use any part of our service available through the Site or other related websites, toolbars, conversion technology, widgets, applications or distribution channels we may operate from (the “Service”). This Policy applies to information that you provide to us through the Site or the Service, when you access or use any content appearing on the Site or made available through the Service, or that we collect on your behalf as part of the Service.  
This Policy is an integral part of our Terms of Service (the “ **Terms of Service** ”). 

##### Changes to this Policy.

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to amend or update this Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Policy, we will post a notice of these changes on our website and in this Policy, and note the effective date of any changes at the top of this page. You are advised to consult this Policy regularly for any changes. If you would like to be notified by email if and when material changes are made to this Policy, please send an email to [legal@duda.co](mailto:legal@duda.co).

#### 2\. Types of Information We Collect

##### Personal Information.

Personal Information is information that specifically identifies you as an individual, including, but not limited to: your name, your mailing address, your telephone number, your mobile number, your e-mail address, your credit card or other billing information, or your company’s name (“ **Personal Information** ”). In the course of using the Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain Personal Information to provide and improve the Service, to contact or identify you and administer your account, to enable you to access certain restricted parts of the Site and the Service, and as otherwise indicated in this Policy.

##### Non-Personal Information.

We also collect information about the use of our Service and the characteristics and activities of users of the Service, from which any personal information has been removed (“ **Non-Personal Information** ”). When you access the Site or use the Service, we may collect the following Non-Personal Information:

  * Information regarding your use of the Service, including, activity and visit behavior on your responsive website or mobile website;
  * Information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or online service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include, but is not limited to: your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, device type, browser type, operating system and version, the web page you were visiting before you came to the Site, information you search for on the Site, locale preferences, identification numbers associated with your Devices, your mobile carrier, date and time stamps associated with transactions, system configuration information, metadata concerning your files, and other interactions with the Service;
  * Your website alias, responsive website or mobile website URL, and website URL; and
  * If you make or a enable a transaction such as a purchase directly from our Site, we will collect billing and financial information as necessary to process your charges, which may include your postal and e-mail addresses.

##### Cookies.

Like many websites, we use “ **cookies** ” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use “ **persistent cookies** ” to save your username and login password for future logins to the Site. We use “ **session ID cookies** ” to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor web traffic routing on the Site and aggregate usage of the Service. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the website you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Service.  
In this Policy, we refer to all information collected from or about you, including but not limited to Personal Information and Non-Personal Information, as “ **Your Information**.”

#### 3\. How We Use Your Information

Your Information is used for, but is not limited to, the following purposes: (i) to provide the Service, (ii) to administer your use of the Service and any accounts you may have with us, (iii) to personalize your experience, (iv) to provide to you service announcements, (v) to provide you with further information and offers from us or third parties that we believe you may find useful or interesting, such as newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, (vi) on behalf of and according to instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners, (vii) to enforce our Terms of Service, (viii) to resolve any disputes between users of the Site or between such users and us, and (ix) to contact you to obtain feedback from you regarding the Site and the Service.

**If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such contact, announcements, information or offers, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in the communication.**  
We use Non-Personal Information for the above purposes and in addition in order to (i) monitor and analyze use of the Service and for the technical administration of the Site, (ii) improve the Site and the Service, (iii) generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of our users, and (iv) verify that users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests.

##### Site Specific Services.

We may post additional ancillary privacy notices with respect to specific services.

##### Links to Other Websites.

We may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed.

##### Third Party Sites.

This Policy applies only to the Site and Service. We do not exercise control over other websites that provide information, or over banners, other advertisements or links from within the Site or the Service. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer’s browser, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Information that you submit, and the collection and use of such information and access of any third party websites are subject to such third party's privacy policy. **We encourage you to read the privacy policies and other terms of such third parties' websites before using their services.**

#### 4\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

##### Disclosure by You of Information of Other Users.

The sending of unwanted messages from one user to another is strictly forbidden. Personal Information of another user obtained through your use of the Site or the Service may be used by you only for the purpose for which such information was provided to you and strictly in accordance with the Terms of Service and this Policy, or otherwise subject to such user’s prior written consent.

##### Your Submissions.

Any information you choose to provide in a comment or a submission on the Site or the Service will be publicly available and should reflect how much you want other users to know about you. **We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and we encourage you to think carefully about what information about yourself you disclose in your comments or submissions.** If you disclose your Personal Information to others, whether or not they are users of the Site, on our Site or through the Service or otherwise, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them.

##### Service Providers.

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to assist us in analyzing how the Service is used, and to perform services related to administration of the Service or the Site (including, without limitation, maintenance, payments, hosting and database management services, website analytics and administration). These third parties may have access to your Personal Information so that they may perform these tasks on our behalf; they are obligated to comply with this Policy and may not use Your Information for any other purpose.

##### Affiliates and Partners.

We may provide Your Information to our affiliates or partners, if (i) you have a relationship with that affiliate or partner either online or off-line (non-Internet), (ii) if you have visited the affiliate or partner's web site that links to or mentions our web site, or (iii) if you have registered for our Services through the partner or affiliate’s program or web site.

##### Non-Personal Information and Aggregate Information.

We may, from time to time, share Non-Personal Information and/or aggregated information. The Non-Personal Information that we share may include, but not be limited to: original website URL, Responsive Website Builder or Mobile Website Builder URL, percentage of active redirects, date of responsive website or Mobile website built, site category type, user category type, performance data, reports generated as a result of your use of the Service that includes non-identifying information, and other Log Data. This shared information may be used for industry analysis, demographic profiling, other commercial purposes and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services. Any information shared in these contexts will **not** contain your Personal Information.

##### Combined Information.

We may combine certain Personal Information with Non-Personal Information in order to allow us to create information packages and services that are better tailored to your interests and preferences. Among other things, linking this information may allow us generally to improve and personalize the Site and the Service. If we combine or link any information with your Personal Information, the resulting combination will be treated as Personal Information under this Policy.

##### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement.

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect our or a third party's property and rights, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable. We also may be required to disclose an individual’s personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. Duda is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

##### Business Transfers.

We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including among others your Personal Information, Non-Personal Information and Log Data, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of all or substantially all of our shares or assets, or in the event of our bankruptcy.

If we ever were to engage in any onward transfers of your data with third parties for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized, we would provide you with an opt-out choice to limit the use and disclosure of your personal data.

In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU or Swiss individuals received pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, Duda is potentially liable.

**We encourage you to consider carefully what information to share as part of your Account profile and elsewhere in the Service, and we recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and not use your real name as your username, as that may allow other users of the Service to identify you. Any information you choose to share should reflect how much you want other users of the Service to know about you. You can review and revise your Account profile information at any time.**

#### 5\. Changing or Deleting Your Information

You may review, update, correct or delete Your Information, if not required to be retained by law or for legitimate business reasons. If you completely delete all such information, your account may be deactivated. In addition, we may delete any information provided by you or related to you, pursuant to our policies as then in effect.

Duda acknowledges that EU and Swiss individuals have the right to access the personal information/data that we maintain about them. An EU or Swiss individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct his query to legal@duda.co. If requested to remove or amend data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

#### 6\. Our Policy Toward Children

We understand the importance of protecting children’s privacy, especially in an online environment. The Site and Services are not designed for or directed at children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from minors. If you are a minor over the age of 13, we recommend you seek consent from a parent or legal guardian before accessing our Service. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [legal@duda.co](mailto:legal@duda.co).

#### 7\. Security

We are committed to safeguarding Your Information. We employ a variety of measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access and disclosure. We make good faith efforts to store Your Information collected on the Service in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to overcome those measures or use your Personal Information for improper purposes, and we do not promise that your Personal Information or private communications will be protected from unauthorized disclosure or use. PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY PRIVILEGED INFORMATION ON THE SITE OR WHEN USING THE SERVICE.

If you receive an e-mail asking you to update your Personal Information, do not reply and please contact us at [legal@duda.co](mailto:legal@duda.co).

#### 8\. International Processing or Transfer

By visiting our Site, using our Service and/or providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that some of Your Information may be transmitted outside your resident jurisdiction and that Your Information may be processed, maintained or transferred outside of your state, where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.

##### Privacy Shield Frameworks

Duda Inc. complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Duda Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Duda Inc. commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Duda Inc. at: 

Duda Legal Department  
577 College Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94306  
legal@duda.co  
+1.866.776.1550 

Duda Inc. has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles to BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/ for more information and to file a complaint. 

Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel. 

#### 9\. Contacting Us

If you have any concerns or questions about this Policy, please contact us at [legal@duda.co](mailto:legal@duda.co).
